ADEMOYE OLUWADAMIFOLA MARK

1, Anibaloye Estate, Off Okunfolami Street, Anthony, Lagos, Nigeria. ademoyedamifola@gmail.com +234-8146848651

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Hi, I'm Mark Ademoye. I am an individual who is interested in quality assurance, automation testing, data mining and software development. I have worked on a few projects that have allowed me to further hone my skills and I strive to work on more in order to improve my technique and reach my goals. Feel free to get in touch if you're interested in working together.

EDUCATION

Apostolic Faith Secondary School, Anthony, Lagos State, Nigeria. Babcock University, Ilishan- Remo, Ogun State, Nigeria.

Program: Bachelor of Science (Hons), Computer

Science.

Academic Standing: Second Class Upper (2:1)

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Academic Award for Best in Further Mathematics- 3 years in a row.
- Research Project on the "Design and Implementation of a Barcode Database Management System"
- Research Project on a "Machine Learning Model for Filtering Inappropriate Language and Hate Speech"
- Research Project on "Building A Model to Identify The Risk Factors Involved In Predicting Early Mutation Of Prostate Cancer"
- Jobberman Certificate of Completion Soft-Skills Training.
- New Horizons Oracle 12C SQL Fundamentals Certificate.
- New Horizons Oracle 12C Administrator Certificate.
- New Horizons Android X8 Development Certificate.
- New Horizons Java SE8 OCA & OCP Certificate.
- New Horizons Installing and Configuring Windows 10 Client Certificate.
- New Horizons CSCU Certificate.
- New Horizons CompTIA A+ Certificate.
- LinkedIn Certificate on 'HTML'.
- ISTQB Certified Foundation Level Tester.

WORK EXPERIENCE

APPLECHOICE LTD. LAGOS ISLAND, LAGOS STATE, NIGERIA June 2016- July 2017

• Tasked with data entry and analysis for the company, it also entailed filing and scanning documents into the system. During this time, I also learnt Blender to design classroom visuals for a project.

MARTAD LTD. MARYLAND, LAGOS STATE, NIGERIA November 2017-February 2018

• Collaborated with other workers to develop functional websites for clients and tested them accordingly.

SEAMFIX LTD. LEKKI, LAGOS STATE, NIGERIA

January 2021- June 2021

• Worked as Quality Assurance Engineer tasked with writing test scripts on multiple modules for web applications and performed periodic manual, functional, integration and automated tests on the websites with various web browsers. During this time, I also performed the duties of a Scrum Master and conducted online meetings for the company.

TECHMAHINDRA. IKOYI, LAGOS STATE, NIGERIA

October 2022- Present

• Performed Quality Assurance tasks mainly centred around manual testing, wrote test scripts on multiple modules for the mobile applications and performed periodic manual and functional tests on the application.

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

Debate President, Babcock University Computer Club, Babcock University September 2021 – May 2022

- Participated in the annual debate competitions between the departments and schools within the university,
- Charged with the training of new aspiring debaters.
- Coordinated events pertaining to the debate and worked closely with other officials.

Head Usher, Babcock University Chapels, Babcock University 2022

September 2018- May

- Directed individuals to their respective seats and ensured that there was decorum in the chapel during the service.
- Coordinated other ushers on how to maintain the church services and also got refreshments for the congregation.

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Academic Tutor, Apostolic Faith Secondary School (2015-2018)
- Represented the Department of Computer Science in the Babcock University Interdepartmental Debate Competition (November 2019).
- Represented the Department of Computer Science in the Babcock University Intradepartmental Debate Competition (July 2019, July 2020).

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office Proficiency (Word, Excel, PowerPoint).
- Communication, Interpersonal and Time Management Skills.
- Proficiency in HTML, CSS, JavaScript Programming.
- Proficiency in Python Programming.
- Proficiency in Java Programming.
- Appium, Selenium and Cypress for Web and Mobile Automation.